<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Nathaniel Keys</title>
    <link>http://localhost:64698/nathanielkeys.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Nathaniel Keys</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:32:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:64698/nathanielkeys.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:64698/nathanielkeys.github.io/beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:32:47 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:64698/nathanielkeys.github.io/beta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nathaniel Keys&#xA;About&#xA;Books&#xA;Large white cumulus clouds against a dark sky.&#xA;Beta reader&#xA;Hello! I’m looking for you to read my new novel before anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Actual Occasions is literary fiction with a lightly speculative pulse, part historical, part contemporary. Think the interwoven resonance of Cloud Atlas or A Visit from the Goon Squad, but told at the intimate, elastic scale of Rachel Cusk’s autofiction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Five strangers in five different eras feel the ground give way beneath them when bridges burn, safe havens disappear, and the same question keeps resurfacing: what do we cling to when the world won’t stay put — memory, myth, or each other?        { 60,000 words }&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://localhost:64698/nathanielkeys.github.io/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:32:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:64698/nathanielkeys.github.io/books/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nathaniel Keys&#xA;About&#xA;Books&#xA;Book cover for &amp;lsquo;The Economics of Carnivory&amp;rsquo; by Nathaniel Keys, featuring a forest with yellow wildflowers in the foreground.&#xA;The Economics of Carnivory&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A wealthy woman in Mississippi falls into a depression, unable to feel basic emotions, and she begins to pickpocket for a rush of adrenaline.&#xA;Buy now&#xA;Open blank notebook with white pages in a black cover on a dark background.&#xA;A/O&#xA;A/O&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Join as a beta reader for a sneak peek, or sign up for the mailing list to be notified when it becomes available.&#xA;Join as a beta reader&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:64698/nathanielkeys.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:30:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:64698/nathanielkeys.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nathaniel Keys&#xA;About&#xA;Books&#xA;About&#xA;Nathaniel Keys is a novelist and essayist whose work explores how emotion and place shape transformation. He earned his Bachelor of Arts in English, summa cum laude, from the University of Southern Mississippi and lives in Portland, Oregon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When he isn’t writing fiction, Nathaniel serves as a senior technical writer in the software industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
